const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'What is the Millenium Falcon?',
    answers: [
      'The origin of the Force',
      'Han Solo\'s spaceship',
      'Boba Fett\'s spaceship',
      'Darth Vader\'s lightsaber'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Han Solo\'s spaceship'
  },
  {
    question: 'Finish this line: “Do. Or do not. _______.”',
    answers: [
      'I am your father',
      'Try not',
      'Do it',
      'There is no try'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'There is no try'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Darth Vader\'s real name?',
    answers: [
      'Ben Skywalker',
      'Wade Wilson',
      'Anakin Skywalker',
      'Qui-Gon Jinn'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Anakin Skywalker'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who are Kylo Ren\'s parents?',
    answers: [
      'Leia Organa and Han Solo',
      'Anakin Skywalker and Padmé Amidala',
      'Owen Lars and Beru Whitesun',
      'Sheev Palpatine and Mon Mothma'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Leia Organa and Han Solo'
  },
  {
    question: 'How did Boba Fett die?',
    answers: [
      'Mace Windu cut off his head',
      'He fell into the Sarlacc\'s pit',
      'Han Solo shot him first',
      'Darth Vader Force choked him'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'He fell into the Sarlacc\'s pit'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the actual purpose of the clone army in episode 3?',
    answers: [
      'To save the galaxy from the Dark Side',
      'To destroy the droid armies',
      'To protect the Galactic Senate',
      'To eliminate the Jedi Order'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'To eliminate the Jedi Order'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many Jedi Masters made up the Jedi High Council?',
    answers: [
      '12',
      '5',
      '10,000',
      '100'
      ],
    correctAnswer: '12'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where did Rey find Luke Skywalker in Episode 7?',
    answers: [
      'At his childhood home on Tatooine',
      'At the first Jedi Temple on Ahch-To',
      'With the Ewoks on the forest moon of Endor',
      'In the remains of the Jedi Temple on Coruscant'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'At the first Jedi Temple on Ahch-To'
  },
  {
    question: 'What classic movie scene was the pod race scene in Episode 1 based on?',
    answers: [
      'The Mexican standoff scene in The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly',
      'The car chase scene in Bullitt',
      'The chariot race scene in Ben Hur',
      'The race scene in Death Race 2000'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'The chariot race scene in Ben Hur'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who shot first: Greedo or Han Solo?',
    answers: [
      'Obviously Han dummy',
      'Greedo (you can\'t be serious...)',
      'It\'s not this answer',
      'It\'s the first answer'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Obviously Han dummy'
  }
];
